beep.com 2018-08-11

# Data privacy declaration - Beep.com

**Assessing and processing of data**

  1. **Access data**

Beepworld GmbH (Beep) collects, uses, stores and transfers your personal data only if this is permitted by law or necessary for the purpose of contract execution or for billing purposes, we will use this to answer your inquiries and / or for technical reasons Need administration or you explicitly agree to the data collection. Your personal data will only be disclosed to third parties or otherwise transmitted, if required by law.   
Every time you access Beepworld websites, access data about this process is stored in so-called log files on our servers. These log files contain the general information that your browser sends to us.   
\- Visited website   
\- Time of the access   
\- Amount of data sent in bytes   
\- message about successful retrieval (HTTP response code)   
\- Source / reference from which you came to the site (Referer)   
\- Browser used and browser version   
\- Operating system used   
\- IP address 

We use this log data without any assignment to you or other profiling for statistical analysis for the purpose of operation, security and optimization of our website. This is also our legitimate interest in accordance with Article 6 paragraph 1 p. 1 f) GDPR.   
Additional personal data will only be collected if you voluntarily provide this information, for example in the context of a request or registration. Beepworld reserves the right to retrospectively check the server logfiles should concrete evidence point to unlawful use.   
You have the right to revoke your consent with effect for the future at any time. This may lead to the fact that we do not provide our services to the full extent z.V. (see point 2).   
Under no circumstances will we pass customer data on to third parties for advertising purposes.   
i. Data to fulfill our contractual obligations   
We process personal data that we need to fulfill our contractual obligations, such as name, address, e-mail address, ordered products, billing and payment data. The collection of this data is required for the conclusion of the contract.   
The deletion of the data takes place after expiry of the warranty periods and legal retention periods. Any data associated with a user account (see below) will in any case be retained for the time this account is maintained.   
The legal basis for the processing of this data is Article 6 (1) sentence 1 (b) GDPR.   
ii. user account   
You can create a user account on our website. If you wish this, we need the personal data requested during the login. Later logins will only require your email or username and the password you have chosen.   
When registering as a member of Beepworld.de you must actively agree to our privacy policy by ticking. We store a customer number, your IP address, e-mail, date and version number of the privacy policy.   
For the new registration we collect master data (for example name, address), communication data (eg e-mail address) and, if necessary, payment data (bank details) as well as access data (user name and password). The passwords selected during registration are automatically encrypted by our system. This procedure ensures that even Beepworld employees can not read out these passwords.   
In order to ensure your proper registration and to prevent unauthorized registrations by third parties, you will receive after your registration an activation link to the deposited e-mail address to activate your account.   
Administration of Beepworld member pages   
As part of our administrative responsibilities and tracking errors, Beepworld employees have access to the administrative portion of the Member Websites. There is insight into all, including the password-protected areas of the website. 

  2. **Utilization of Cookies**

Cookies are small text files that are stored on your computer and stored by your browser. The use of cookies increases the user-friendliness and security of this website.   
Cookies do not harm your computer and do not contain viruses. If you refuse the use of cookies, we ask you to change the settings of your browser. Rejection may result in some areas of our services becoming unavailable. 
  3. **Cookies utilized by Beep**

Cookies are set after visiting the Beepworld main page, logging in to one of our password-protected pages, as well as entering the members area and clicking on the page processing. After switching between mobile and standard view, a cookie is also set.   
To a lesser extent, we also use persistent cookies that remain on your device and allow us to recognize your browser on your next visit. These cookies are stored on your hard drive and delete themselves after the given time. Their lifespan is 1 month to 12 months.   
Our legitimate interest in the use of cookies in accordance with Article 6 para. 1 sentence 1 f) of the DSGVO is to make our website more user-friendly, effective and secure. 
  4. **Cookies utilized by third parties**

We use third-party services. These companies may use information about your visits. Details can be found under point 3. 
  5. **Storage of user information**

Each time you access the member area, relevant data such as actions taken, member name (if applicable), date / time and IP address are stored. In detail, these are: 

i. Handling contact information   
Get in touch with Beepworld GmbH through the offered contact options, e.g. Via the contact form, your details will be stored so that they can be used to process and answer your request. Without your consent, this data will not be disclosed to third parties. Your consent is given by clicking on the checkbox and submitting the form.   
ii. Subscription to the Beep newsletter   
To subscribe to the newsletter you will need the data requested in the registration process. The registration for the newsletter will be logged. After logging in, you will receive a message on the specified email address requesting confirmation of your registration ("Double Opt-in"). This is necessary so that third parties can not register with their email address.   
You can always revoke your consent to receive the newsletter and thus unsubscribe from the newsletter.   
We save the registration details as long as they are needed for sending the newsletter. The logging of the application and the shipping address are stored as long as there was an interest in the proof of the originally given consent, as a rule, these are the limitation periods for civil claims, thus a maximum of three years.   
Legal basis for sending the newsletter is your consent acc. Art. 6 (1) sentence 1 a) in conjunction with Art. 7 DSGVO in conjunction with § 7 (2) no. 3 UWG. Legal basis for logging the application is our legitimate interest in proving that the shipment was made with your consent.   
You can cancel the registration at any time, without incurring any costs other than the transmission costs according to the basic rates. A textual message to the contact details referred to in point 1 (eg e-mail, fax, letter) is sufficient. Of course, you will also find an unsubscribe link in every newsletter or you can unsubscribe from your membership area under PROFILE by unchecking "Receive newsletter from Beepworld.de".   
iii. Registration of top-level domains   
In our paid packages are at least one top level domain endings .de, .com. net, org included. The hosting of the domains takes over the company for us   
Nimblu   
PlusServer GmbH   
Hohenzollernring 72   
50672 Cologne   
At https://www.nimblu.com/impressum-and-lawful   
find the privacy statement of NimBlu 

To register a domain, Beepworld GmbH must forward the necessary data to the responsible registrar. This data may be made public by the registrar.   
iv. Email address   
When registering one or more e-mail accounts via our platform, these accounts are created on an e-mail server operated by Beepworld GmbH itself.   
v. Storage of user content   
The hosting services we use to provide the following services: infrastructure and platform services, computing capacity, storage and database services, security and technical maintenance services we use to operate the site.   
In doing so, we or our hosting provider processes inventory data, contact data, content data, contract data, usage data, meta and communication data of customers, interested parties and visitors to this website based on our legitimate interests in an efficient and secure provision of our website. Art. 6 para. 1 p. 1 f) DSGVO i.V.m. Art. 28 GDPR.   
Beepworld GmbH uses the servers of OVH GmbH to store all user data and page content.   
OVH GmbH in Dudweiler Landstrasse 5, 66123 Saarbruecken, Germany   
The privacy policy of OVH GmbH can be found here: https://www.ovh.de/unternehmen/datenschutz.xml 

**Third-party features that can be inserted via widgets in Beep ´s editor**

i. Youtube   
This website uses the product youtube. YouTube is a big video sharing platform that belongs to Google. All data stored using YouTube will be aggregated into the Google Account. These are in particular personal data including their IP address.   
Embedding YouTube videos on our website is based solely on YouTube's "Advanced Privacy Mode". According to its own information, YouTube stores information about visitors to a website only when they play the corresponding video.   
Learn more at https://support.google.com/youtube/answer/171780?hl=en   
Provider Google LLC, 1600 Amphitheater Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA 

ii. Addthis   
This website uses the Addthis product from Oracle Inc. With the AddThis tools, website operators can enable users to instantly share web pages, blogs, news, photos, videos, and other content through browser or web page plug-ins on the most popular social networks and other destinations divide.   
The privacy statements of addthis can be found here: http://www.addthis.com/privacy/privacy-policy/en/   
Provider Add This   
Oracle America, Inc.,   
1595 Spring Hill Rd, Suite 300, Vienna, VA 22182   
(703) 677-3999 

iii. Google +1   
This website uses Google Inc.'s Google +1 product. If you click on a Google +1 social media button, the plugin will create a direct connection between your browser and Google. The servers of Google can be located in particular also in the USA. Your IP address and other information will be stored by Google. If you withdraw your recommendation by clicking again on the "+ 1-Button", these data will be deleted, according to Google.   
Google also uses cookies to process information about the use of websites. Through the page view, Google may receive the information that you have accessed the relevant website. If you are logged into Google +1 or another Google Account such as YouTube during your visit to our website through your personal user account, Google may assign the website visit to your account. Before you visit our website, it is best to log out of your Google Account to prevent this.   
The information you provide will be used by Google in accordance with their applicable privacy policy: https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en   
Google may also publish and / or share statistics about users' + 1 activity to users and partners, such as publishers, advertisers, or affiliate websites.   
Provider Google LLC, 1600 Amphitheater Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA   
iv. Google Maps   
This website uses the Google Maps API product, a service provided by Google Inc. to display an interactive map. By using Google Maps, personally identifiable information about your use of this website (including your IP address) may be transmitted to Google's servers in the United States and stored there.   
You can find the Terms of Use for Google Maps at the following link: https://www.google.com/intl/en_uk/help/terms_maps.html   
Provider: Google LLC, 1600 Amphitheater Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA   
v. Twitter   
This website uses the Twitter product from Twitter Inc.   
By clicking on the "Widget" you can e.g. Send a link to the web page you are currently on as the content of a tweet via your Twitter account. When accessing these web pages, if there is a "widget" from Twitter on the web site, it will connect to Twitter's servers, which may also be in the US.   
By using Twitter, the websites you visit are linked to your Twitter account and shared with other users. Personal data will also be transmitted to Twitter, such as your IP address, the browser type, the operating system and the address of the website on which Twitter's widget is located.   
In addition, a cookie is set in the browser of your device via the "Widget" of Twitter. The exact privacy policy of Twitter can be found here:   
https://twitter.com/privacy?lang=de   
Provider in Europe: Twitter Inc. One Cumberland Place, Fenian Street Dublin 2, D02 AX07 Ireland   
vi. PayPal   
This website uses the product PayPal. PayPal collects personal information from you when you visit PayPal Sites or use its services. This includes the following information:   
\- Information about registration and use, transactions and experiences   
\- personal data:   
\- of transaction participants   
\- through your friends and contacts who you provide PayPal to receive additional services or specific online services   
\- via you, when you make a transaction as a guest   
\- through you from third parties   
\- other information that PayPal collects when you use Paypal's websites or services   
In detail you will find the information collected by PayPal here:   
https://www.paypal.com/at/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-prev?locale.x=de 

The list of third parties (other than PayPal customers) with whom PayPal may share personal information can be found here: https://www.paypal.com/ie/webapps/mpp/ua/third-parties-list   
Provider: PayPal (Europe) S.à r.l. et Cie, S.C.A.   
22-24 Boulevard Royal   
L-2449 Luxembourg   
E-Mail: impressum@paypal.com 

vii. Facebook   
This website uses social plugins of the social network facebook.com, which is operated by Facebook Inc.   
When our website or that of our members is called, which contains such a plugin, the browser establishes a direct connection with the servers of Facebook. The content of the plugin is transmitted by Facebook directly to the browser and incorporated by him into the website. By integrating the plugins, Facebook receives the information that the corresponding page of our website has been accessed by the respective visitor or Beepworld user. If Facebook has its own Facebook profile, Facebook may associate the visit with cookies or using JavaScript to the visitor's Facebook account or Beepworld user.   
When interacting with the plugins, for example, clicking the "like / like" button or leaving a comment, the corresponding information is transmitted from the browser directly to Facebook and stored there. Do you want to prevent the Facebook. Inc. associates this information with your Facebook account, please log out of Facebook before visiting this website. This can also be prevented with suitable browser plugins; in that case, it may be that the Facebook social plugins no longer work.   
The purpose and scope of the data collection and the further processing and use of the data by Facebook, as well as your related rights and privacy settings can be found in the Facebook Privacy Policy at https://de-de.facebook.com/policy.php   
Provider in Europe:   
Facebook Ireland Ltd.   
4 Grand Canal Square   
Grand Canal Harbor   
Dublin 2 Ireland
